(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)No one does a better job
(Sheldon:)pretending to be a person
than I do.
(Sheldon:)Siri comes close,
but I know more jokes.
(Howard:)If you don't want to
use dating Web sites,
(Howard:)what do you suggest?
(Sheldon:)Off the top of my head?
Uh, prospective women
(Sheldon:)weed themselves out
in a battle of wits
(Sheldon:)until only one champion remains,
(Sheldon:)she shows up at my door flush
with the thrill of victory,
(Sheldon:)and then sits quietly by my side
while I watch Daredevil.
(Howard:)You seriously think women
would fight for you?
(Sheldon:)People compete for jobs
and trophies... why not me?
(Howard:)He's right... he knows
a lot of jokes.
(Raj:)Yeah... no, but it is
basic human nature.
(Raj:)If we present him as a prize,
maybe they would.
(Howard:)Well, he's smart,
(Howard:)he's a respected
scientist...
And I have
the soulful eyes of a cow.
(Raj:)I don't know
if I'd say you...
(Penny:)Oh.